{"classes":["GADGET","VIDEOGAME","ORG","PERSON","MOVIE","NATURE","DATE","MONUMENT","LOCATION","ART","COUNTRY","SPORT"],"annotations":[["Apple is launching the new HomePod.\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[27,34,"GADGET"]]}],["Steam is launching the new gaming device SteamDeck.\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[41,50,"GADGET"]]}],["Nintendo offers a gaming console known as Switch.\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[42,48,"GADGET"]]}],["Counter Strike is a popular video game.\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"VIDEOGAME"]]}],["Valorant is a popular video game.\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"VIDEOGAME"]]}],["Apple makes great phones.\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"]]}],["Steam has a great market.\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"]]}],["Valorant is played by many people.\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"VIDEOGAME"]]}],["LG makes good Televisions.\r",{"entities":[[0,2,"ORG"],[14,25,"GADGET"]]}],["HP Laptops are good.\r",{"entities":[[0,2,"ORG"],[3,10,"GADGET"]]}],["Razer makes good quality mouse.\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[25,30,"GADGET"]]}],["Logitech G402 mouse is still a really good mouse.\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[9,19,"GADGET"]]}],["The CEO of Apple, Tim Cook, announced a new product at the company's annual event.\r",{"entities":[[11,16,"ORG"],[18,26,"PERSON"]]}],["Emma Stone won an Academy Award for Best Actress in a Leading Role for her performance in \"La La Land\".\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[91,101,"ART"]]}],["Leonardo da Vinci began painting the Mona Lisa about 1503.\r",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[37,46,"ART"]]}],["Robert Downey Jr. played Ironman for the last time in Avengers: End Game.\r",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[54,72,"ART"]]}],["Silicon Valley is in USA.\r",{"entities":[[21,24,"COUNTRY"]]}],["Cricket is very famous in India.\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"SPORT"],[26,31,"COUNTRY"]]}],["Serena Williams is a good player of tennis.\r",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[36,42,"SPORT"]]}],["Formula 1 is going to Australia this weekend.\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"SPORT"],[22,31,"COUNTRY"]]}],["Hockey is the national sport of India.\r",{"entities":[[0,6,"SPORT"],[32,37,"COUNTRY"]]}],["Chris Gayle is a cricket player from West Indies.\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[37,48,"COUNTRY"]]}],["This year cricket world cup will be in India.\r",{"entities":[[10,17,"SPORT"],[39,44,"COUNTRY"]]}],["Satya Nadella is the CEO of Microsoft.\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[28,37,"ORG"]]}],["Sundar Pichai is the CEO of Google.\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[28,34,"ORG"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}